Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies Records UA153
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies Records
2005 -- 2008
2003 -- 2008
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
UA153
5.55 Linear Feet 6 boxes
115 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
The collection is organized into seven series: Student research and proposals; Grant proposals and information; Administrative files; Courses; Conferences; Website; and Unprocessed accessions.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes reports, presentations, publications, websites, and other documentation relating to the functions of the Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies.
Biographical / Historical
The Jebsen Center for Counter-Terrorism Studies was established at The Fletcher School in September, 2005 with a gift by Mr. Jan Henrik Jebsen, Chairman of the Gamma Applied Visions Group, a Swiss holding company. The Center was led by Director Brigadier General (retired) Russell Howard, Associate Director Paula Broadwell, Associate Director Stacy Neal, and Staff Assistant Jeannine Lenehan. Its mission was to increase the understanding and competency of counter-terrorism professionals. To accomplish this mission the Jebsen Center funded a robust research and analysis program, hosted conferences and a visiting fellows program, and conducted outreach activities. The early research topics at the Center focused on predicting, preventing and preempting terrorist activity, as well as understanding the role of women and business in the campaign against terrorism. The Jebsen Center closed in September 2008.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details
Curriculum and Instruction -- Academic Centers and Institutes; Foreign affairs; Curriculum and Instruction -- Student Work
- Student Research and Proposals, 2005 -- 2008; UA153.001; 2.4 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains original notes, reports, publications, and correspondence created by graduate students at the Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies. Includes work done by students for publication and work done towards earning grants, funding, internships, and fellowships. Student curriculum vitaes are also present in most folders. Also contains student proposals for studies and research that were rejected.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Human bombs, Nicole Argo [External material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Human bombs, Nicole Argo [Binder material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Human bombs, Nicole Argo [Back cover material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Funded research, Natasha Bajema [External material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Funded research, Natasha Bajema [Binder material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Funded research, Natasha Bajema [Back cover material], 2007; UA153.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Emma Belcher's research [External material], 2007; UA153.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Emma Belcher's research [Front cover material], 2007; UA153.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Emma Belcher's research [Binder material], 2007; UA153.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Benedetta Alberti's research [External material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Benedetta Alberti's research [Binder material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Benedetta Alberti's research [Back cover material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Paula Broadwell's research [External material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Paula Broadwell's research [Front cover binder], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Paula Broadwell's research [Binder material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Kate Brodock's research [External material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Kate Brodock's research [Front cover material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Kate Brodock's research [Binder material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Kate Brodock's research [Back cover material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Jennifer Buntman's research [External material], 2007; UA153.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Jennifer Buntman's research [Binder material], 2007; UA153.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Jennifer Buntman's research [Back cover material], 2007; UA153.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - CAPS [External material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - CAPS [Binder material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Erica Chenoweth's research [External material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Erica Chenoweth's research [Front cover material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Erica Chenoweth's research [Binder material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Erica Chenoweth's research [Back cover material], 2007; UA153.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Matan Chorev's research [External material], 2005 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Matan Chorev's research [Front cover material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Matan Chorev's research [Binder material], 2005 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Matan Chorev's research [Back cover material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Erosion of constraints [External material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Erosion of constraints [Binder material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Funded research Gregory Dimitriadis [External material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Funded research Gregory Dimitriadis [Front cover material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Funded research Gregory Dimitriadis [Binder material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Funded research Gregory Dimitriadis [Back cover material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Muslim women suicide bombers and their relationship to the jihad [External material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - Muslim women suicide bombers and their relationship to the jihad [Binder material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - Guatemala, Laurie Gagnon [External material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Guatemala, Laurie Gagnon [Binder material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - Guatemala, Laurie Gagnon [Back cover material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - Joshua Gleis [External material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - Joshua Gleis [Binder material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - Joshua Gleis [Back cover material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00046 (Box 1)
  - Stephen Heitkamp [External material], 2007; UA153.001.001.00047 (Box 1)
  - Stephen Heitkamp [Binder material], 2007; UA153.001.001.00048 (Box 1)
  - U.S. rural economic development policy in Afghanistan [External material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00049 (Box 1)
  - U.S. rural economic development policy in Afghanistan [Front cover material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00050 (Box 1)
  - U.S. rural economic development policy in Afghanistan [Binder material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00051 (Box 1)
  - U.S. rural economic development policy in Afghanistan [Back cover material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00052 (Box 1)
  - Farheen Khan [External material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00053 (Box 1)
  - Farheen Khan [Binder Material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00054 (Box 1)
  - Farheen Khan [Back cover material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00055 (Box 1)
  - Kei Koga [External material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.001.001.00056 (Box 1)
  - Kei Koga [Binder material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.001.001.00057 (Box 1)
  - Kei Koga [Back cover material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.001.001.00058 (Box 1)
  - Itamara Lochard [External material], 2005 -- 2006; UA153.001.001.00059 (Box 1)
  - Itamara Lochard [Binder material], 2005 -- 2006; UA153.001.001.00060 (Box 1)
  - Ed Locke [External material], 2007; UA153.001.001.00061 (Box 1)
  - Ed Locke [Binder material], 2007; UA153.001.001.00062 (Box 1)
  - Assaf Moghadam [External material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00063 (Box 1)
  - Assaf Moghadam [Front cover material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00064 (Box 1)
  - Assaf Moghadam [Binder material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00065 (Box 1)
  - Assaf Moghadam [Back cover material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00066 (Box 1)
  - Michael Mylrea [External material], 2007; UA153.001.001.00067 (Box 1)
  - Michael Mylrea [Binder material], 2007; UA153.001.001.00068 (Box 1)
  - Ronnie Olesker [External material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00069 (Box 1)
  - Ronnie Olesker [Front cover material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00070 (Box 1)
  - Ronnie Olesker [Binder material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00071 (Box 1)
  - Ronnie Olesker [Back cover material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00072 (Box 1)
  - Natalie Parke [External material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.001.001.00073 (Box 1)
  - Natalie Parke [Binder material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.001.001.00074 (Box 1)
  - Natalie Parke [Back cover material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.001.001.00075 (Box 1)
  - Perserec [External material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00076 (Box 1)
  - Perserec [Binder material], 2006; UA153.001.001.00077 (Box 1)
  - Tzonivar (Sonya) Ramian [External material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.001.001.00078 (Box 1)
  - Tzonivar (Sonya) Ramian [Binder material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.001.001.00079 (Box 1)
  - Tzonivar (Sonya) Ramian [Back cover material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.001.001.00080 (Box 1)
  - Sharon Rivera [External material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00081 (Box 1)
  - Sharon Rivera [Front cover material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00082 (Box 1)
  - Sharon Rivera [Binder material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00083 (Box 1)
  - Sharon Rivera [Back cover material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.001.00084 (Box 1)
  - Countering ideological support [External material], 2007; UA153.001.002.00001 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Countering ideological support [Front cover material], 2007; UA153.001.002.00002 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Countering ideological support [Binder material], 2007; UA153.001.002.00003 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Securing the US-Mexico border [External material], 2008; UA153.001.002.00004 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Securing the US-Mexico border [Front cover material], 2008; UA153.001.002.00005 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Securing the US-Mexico border [Binder material], 2008; UA153.001.002.00006 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Funded research Hilary Sienrukos [External material], 2006; UA153.001.002.00007 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Funded research Hilary Sienrukos [Front cover material], 2008; UA153.001.002.00008 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Funded research Hilary Sienrukos [Binder material], 2008; UA153.001.002.00009 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Funded research Hilary Sienrukos [Back cover material], 2008; UA153.001.002.00010 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Funded research Colleen Traughber [External material], 2006; UA153.001.002.00011 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Funded research Colleen Traughber, 2006; UA153.001.002.00012 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Funded research Colleen Traughber [Back cover material], 2006; UA153.001.002.00013 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Funded research Lorenzo Vidino [External material], 2006; UA153.001.002.00014 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Funded research Lorenzo Vidino [Binder material], 2006; UA153.001.002.00015 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Funded research Lorenzo Vidino [Binder materials], 2006; UA153.001.002.00016 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Funded research Rockford Weitz [External material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.002.00017 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Funded research Rockford Weitz [Binder material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.002.00018 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Funded research Rockford Weitz [Back cover material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.001.002.00019 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Jebsen center spring-summer 2008 research funding spreadsheet, UA153.001.002.00020 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Rejected research proposals [External material], 2005 -- 2006; UA153.001.002.00021 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Rejected research proposals [Binder material], 2005 -- 2006; UA153.001.002.00022 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - 2007 summer interns [External material], UA153.001.002.00023 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - 2007 summer interns [Front cover material], UA153.001.002.00024 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - 2007 summer interns [Binder material], UA153.001.002.00025 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - 2007 summer interns [Binder material], UA153.001.002.00026 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - 2007 summer interns [Binder material], UA153.001.002.00027 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
- Grant Proposals and Information, 2005 -- 2008; UA153.002; 2.4 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains original research, proposals and correspondence between the Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies and funding institutions. The proposals were created to generate grant funding for research within the Jebsen Center on topics dealing with terrorism and counter-terrorism. Correspondance is between the Jebsen Center and funding institutions regarding fund payments and the status of research. There is also research done by the Jebsen Center on potential funding institutions.
  20 years from date of creation. Open for research.
  - Jebsen center [External material], 2005; UA153.002.002.00028 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Jebsen center [Front cover materials], 2005; UA153.002.002.00029 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Jebsen center [Binder materials], 2005; UA153.002.002.00030 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Jebsen center [Back cover material], 2005; UA153.002.002.00031 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Grant and contract processing information [External material], 2006; UA153.002.002.00032 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Grant and contract processing information [Binder material], 2006; UA153.002.002.00033 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Bradley foundation [External material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.002.002.00034 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Bradley foundation [Binder material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.002.002.00035 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Bradley grant [External material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.002.002.00036 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Bradley grant [Front cover material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.002.002.00037 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Bradley grant [Binder material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.002.002.00038 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - [Bradley foundation] Final report to the Lynde and Harry Bradley foundation [External material], 2006 -- 2008; UA153.002.002.00039 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - [Bradley foundation] Final report to the Lynde and Harry Bradley foundation [Front cover material], 2006 -- 2008; UA153.002.002.00040 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - [Bradley foundation] Final report to the Lynde and Harry Bradley foundation [Binder material], 2006 -- 2008; UA153.002.002.00041 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - [Bradley foundation] Financial summary reports [External material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.002.002.00042 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - [Bradley foundation] Financial summary reports [Front cover material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.002.002.00043 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - [Bradley foundation] Financial summary reports [Binder material], 2006 -- 2007; UA153.002.002.00044 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Henry Luce foundation [External material], 2007; UA153.002.002.00045 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Henry Luce foundation [Binder material], 2007; UA153.002.002.00046 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Human security and terrorism [External material], 2007; UA153.002.002.00047 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Human security and terrorism [Front cover material], 2007; UA153.002.002.00048 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Human security and terrorism [Binder material 1], 2005 -- 2007; UA153.002.002.00049 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Human security and terrorism [Binder material 2], 2005 -- 2007; UA153.002.002.00050 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Human security and terrorism [Binder material 3], 2005 -- 2007; UA153.002.002.00051 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Madrasas [External material], 2006; UA153.002.002.00052 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Madrasas [Front cover material], 2006; UA153.002.002.00053 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Madrasas [Binder material 1], 2005 -- 2006; UA153.002.002.00054 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Madrasas [Binder material 2], 2005 -- 2006; UA153.002.002.00055 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Maritime security Sayres and associates corp. [External material], 2007; UA153.002.002.00056 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Maritime security Sayres and asso. corp. [Binder material], 2007; UA153.002.002.00057 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Stacy Reiter Neal [External material], 2005 -- 2006; UA153.002.002.00058 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Stacy Reiter Neal [Front cover material], 2005 -- 2006; UA153.002.002.00059 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Stacy Reiter Neal [Binder material], 2005 -- 2006; UA153.002.002.00060 (Box UA153 Shared 1)
  - Perserec financial report [External material], 2007; UA153.002.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Perserec Project [Binder material], 2007; UA153.002.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Perserec [External material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Perserec [Front cover material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Perserec [Binder material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Perserec, 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - ProTechT solutions [External materials], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - ProTechT solutions [Front cover materials], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - ProTechT solutions [Binder materials 1], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - ProTechT solutions [Binder materials 2], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - ProTechT solutions [Back cover material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - [ProTechT solutions] Final reports to ProTechT solutions, S.A. [External material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - [ProTechT solutions] Final reports to ProTechT solutions, S.A., 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - [ProTechT solutions] Final reports to ProTecht solutions, S.A., 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Sloan foundation [External material], 2005 -- 2006; UA153.002.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Sloan foundation [Binder material 1], 2005 -- 2006; UA153.002.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Sloan foundation [Binder material 2], 2005 -- 2006; UA153.002.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Synexxus, Inc. Africa research project [External material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Synexxus, Inc. Africa research project [Front cover material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Synexxus, Inc. Africa research project [Binder material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Transnational crime binder 1 [External material], 2007; UA153.002.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Transnational crime binder 1 [Binder material 1], 2007; UA153.002.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Transnational crime binder 1 [Binder material 2], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Transnational crime binder 2 [External material], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Transnational crime binder 2 [Binder material 1], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Transnational crime binder 2 [Binder material 2], 2007 -- 2008; UA153.002.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - U.S. muslim diaspora [External material], 2006; UA153.002.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - U.S. muslim diaspora [Front cover material], 2006; UA153.002.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - U.S. muslim diaspora [Binder material 1], 2006; UA153.002.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - U.S. muslim diaspora [Binder material 2], 2006; UA153.002.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Grants, Gifts, Subcontracts, 2005 -- 2008; UA153.002.011.00001; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies; 1 Digital Object(s)
    20 years from date of creation.
    Folders containing files that were not compatible with preservation formats: ProTechT has regular PDFs, .jpg, and .wmv files; Synexxus has PDFs; Foundations has PDFs; Bradley Foundation has PDFs; Fletcher Policy has .jpg and .htm; Human Security and Terrorism has PDFs; JHJ has .jpg; Luce Foundation has .eml; Madrasas has .htm and PDFs; PERSEREC has PDFs, .css, .gif, and .js; PV3103 has .jpg; Sloan Foundation has PDFs, .mdi; Transnational Crime has PDFs, .xfd; TSWG has PDFs; U.S. Muslims Diaspora has PDFs and .xfs; Tufts Paperwork has PDFs and .eml
- Administrative, 2005 -- 2008; UA153.003; 62 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains weekly activity reports and financial reports for the Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies between 2005 and 2008. The activity reports track the work and progress of staff members, researchers, and student fellows. Financial reports deal with the allocation of funds for salaries, wages, travel, and research.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report, October 10-14, 2005; UA153.003.004.00001; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report, October 31 - November 9, 2005; UA153.003.004.00002; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report November 14-18, 2005; UA153.003.004.00003; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report November 21-25, 2005; UA153.003.004.00004; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
    Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report November 28 - December 2, 2005; UA153.003.004.00005; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report December 5 - 9, 2005; UA153.003.004.00006; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report December 12 - 16, 2005; UA153.003.004.00007; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report December 19 - December 23, 2005; UA153.003.004.00008; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report January 30 - February 3, 2006; UA153.003.004.00009; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report February 13 - 17, 2006; UA153.003.004.00010; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report February 20 - 24, 2006; UA153.003.004.00011; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report February 27 - March 3, 2006; UA153.003.004.00012; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report March 6 - 10, 2006; UA153.003.004.00013; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report March 13 - 17, 2006; UA153.003.004.00014; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report March 27 - 31, 2006; UA153.003.004.00015; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report April 3-7, 2006; UA153.003.004.00016; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report April 10-14, 2006; UA153.003.004.00017; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report April 17 - 21, 2006; UA153.003.004.00018; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report April 24-28, 2006; UA153.003.004.00019; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report May 1-5, 2006; UA153.003.004.00020; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report May 8-12, 2006; UA153.003.004.00021; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report May 15-19, 2006; UA153.003.004.00022; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report May 22-26, 2006; UA153.003.004.00023; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report June 5 -16, 2006; UA153.003.004.00024; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies